Guide to the Duke University Union Records, 1954-ongoing UA.09.13.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Records1954-ongoing, 54 boxes
  - Selection, 1998 (Box 51)
  - Finance: Approved Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Finance: Miscellaneous Union Information, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Finance: Summer Proposals, 1997 (Box 51)
  - Finance: General, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Finance: End of Year Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, Fall 1997 (Box 51)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, Spring 1998 (Box 51)
  - Finance: General Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Cable 13: Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Cable 13: Finances, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Homecoming, 1998 (Box 51)
  - University Union Board: CFO Handbooks, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Cable 13: Miscellaneous/General, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Finance: Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 1998 (Box 51)
  - Special Events: Springfest, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Archiving Project, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Chronicle Ads, 1997-1999 (Box 51)
  - Old Logos, 1970s-1990s (Box 51)
  - Retreat Information and Evaluations, 1980s-1990s (Box 51)
  - Slides potentially for Chronicle Ads, circa mid-1990s (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Handbook, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Slide Log, 1993-1999 (Box 51)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Facilities: Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Finance: Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Minutes [various committees], 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - New Computer, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Equipment Proposals, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Endowment, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Approved Programming Proposals, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - General Fund, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Budget Proposals, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - University Union Board Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
  - Playbills/Performance Ephemera, 1980s-1990s (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Janna Stern, August 29-September 26, 1998 (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Richard Marshall, September 29-October 30, 1998 (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Wake Up, Little Suzy, November 9-December 7, 1998 (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Peyton Russo, December 12, 1998-January 15, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Willie Hooker, February 5-March 5, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Helen Marie Smith, March 29-April 30, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Tom Kregel, June 7-July 16, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Visual Arts: Dalton and Steele, July 26-September 3, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Selection, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Craft Center: Bryan Center Space, 1999 (Box 51)
  - Creating the Budget, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - Facilities: Pianos on West Campus, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - Finance: Budget, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - University Union Board Meeting Materials, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - University Union Board, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - Summer Letters, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - Endowment Drive, circa 2000 (Box 52)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 1999 (Box 52)
  - Special Events: Dance Marathon, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Handbook, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - Alumni Packet, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - Leadership Development Assessment Results, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
  - University Union Board Miscellany, 1998-2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Brent Sackmon, September 9-October 1, 1999 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Annabelle Meacham, October 4-29, 1999 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Susan Simone, November 1-December 3, 1999 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Wolf Bolz, December 6, 1999-January 14, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Melissa Smith, January 17-February 18, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Amy Levine, February 21-March 17, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Uri Katzenstein, March 19-April 2, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Policy Committee: Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Facilities: Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Finance: Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - DSG By-Laws, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Endowment Information, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - University Union Board Materials, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Finance: Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - University Union Board Miscellany, 1989-2001 (Box 52)
  - Special Events: Fall Forum, September 16, 2000 (Box 52)
  - College Emmy Information, circa 2000 (Box 52)
  - Cable 13: Chuck Henage/MHT of NC, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Cable 13: Meetings/Brainstorms, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Cable 13: Publicity/Advertising, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Facilities: Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Major Attractions, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Broadway at Duke: Year-End Report, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Special Events: Springternational, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Special Events, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Duke Student Government: Financial Aid Task Force, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Finance: Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest T-Shirt Ideas, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Retreat February, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Alumni ReUnion, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Applications [various positions], 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Union Logos, all committees, undated (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Graduation with Distinction, April 10-May 14, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Scott Little, May 22-June 30, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Marvin Saltzman, July 10-September 1, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: David Terry, September 4-29, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Keith Peoples, October 2-27, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Gail Watkins, October 30-December 1, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Fall Student Show, December 3-16, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Bay Valley 5, January 8-February 16, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Emily Weinstein, February 19-March 19, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Bryant Holsenbeck, March 19-April 14, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Senior Distinction Show, April 16-May 15, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Margie Stewart, May 23-June 30, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Visual Arts: Gary Pohl, July 9-August 31, 2001 (Box 52)
  - Programming: Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 52)
  - Officers, 2001-2002 (Box 54)
  - Finance: Budget, 2001-2002 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 2001 (Box 54)
  - WXDU, 2001-2002 (Box 54)
  - Financial Aid Policy Report and Analysis, 2001-2002 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Springternational, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Cable 13: External Proposals, 2001-2002 (Box 54)
  - Tom Cookerly: Alumni Network, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Cable 13: Miscellaneous/General, 2001-2004 (Box 54)
  - Cable 13: Policy, 1997-2002 (Box 54)
  - Facilities: Agendas, Materials, Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 54)
  - Cable 13: Recent Orders, 1999-2002 (Box 54)
  - Summer Programming, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Retreat, Fall 2002 (Box 54)
  - Fee Increase, 2002 (Box 54)
  - WEL Kickoff, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Hal Kammerer Scholarship, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Aristides Logothetis, September 2-29, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Vickie Mitchell, October 1-27, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Paris Alexander, October 29-November 30, 2001 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Easton Davy, January 8-February 8, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Karen Hamner, February 11-March 15, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Vincent Hron, March 18-April 12, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Senior Distinction Show, April 15-May 15, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Christine Basick, May 24-July 13, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Suzanne Stryk, July 17-August 30, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Cable 13: Endowment Funds, 1997-2002 (Box 54)
  - Constitution, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Semester Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 54)
  - Cable 13: Station Re-wire, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Cable 13: Devil Time, 2002-2003 (Box 54)
  - University Union Board: Proposals, 1998-2003 (Box 54)
  - Cable 13: Meetings, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Facilities: Approved Space Applications, 2002-2003 (Box 54)
  - University Union Board Minutes and Miscellany, 2002-2003 (Box 54)
  - Facilities: Denied Space Applications, 2002-2003 (Box 54)
  - Changeover, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Arthur Huang, September 2-28, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: David Gista, September 30-October 26, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Randy Polumbo, October 28-November 23, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: KYLE, November 25-December 23, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Aaron Lee Benson, January 10-February 15, 2003 (Box 54)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 54)
  - University Union Board: Appointments, 1995-2002 (Box 54)
  - Finance: Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 2002 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Devil Hunt, 2003 (Box 54)
  - University Union Board Miscellany, circa mid-2000s (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Wendell Smith, February 17-March 14, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Ken Courtney, March 17-April 12, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Senior Distinction Show, April 14-May 14, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Mia Brownell, May 22-June 30, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Rachel Abrams, July-August 29, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Priscilla Troy, September 2-26, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Gene Hollander, September 29-October 23, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Katherine Grossfield, October 24-November 21, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Lisa Salosaari Jasinski, November 24-December 19, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Jeffrey Whittle, January 8-February 6, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: The Names Project (AIDS Quilt), February 8-14, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Jonathan Blackwell, February 16-March 12, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Barbara Rachko, March 15-April 9, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Security-Comforts and Costs, April 2, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Senior Distinction Show, April 12-May 12, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Mark Gordon, May 24-July 5, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Finance: Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Springternational, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Selection, 2003 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 2004 (Box 54)
  - Visual Arts: Jo Owens Murphy, 2004-2005 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Springternational, 2005 (Box 54)
  - 50th Anniversary, 2005-2006 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest Vendor Registration, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest Vendor Reimbursement, 2005 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Springternational Vendor Registration, 2006 (Box 54)
  - Special Events: Springternational, 2006 (Box 54)
- Visual Materials and Photographs 1954-2010, 3 boxes
  Contains photographs, slides, and other visual materials and objects from events sponsored by the Duke University Union, primarily dating from the 1950s through the 1990s.
  - Slides, undated, from various Union events. Primarily 1950s-1970s. (Box V1)
  - Plaque: 1st Place Table Tennis Tournament, 1962-1963 (Box V2)
  - Undergraduate Student Government Reception for the Duke Board of Trustees, February 28, 1963 (Box V2)
  - Andre Leon Gray, February 2-28, 1998 (Box V2)
  - Shirley Little, December 19, 1997-January 31, 1998 (Box V2)
  - Gayle Stott Lowry, November 10-December 16, 1997 (Box V2)
  - Joanie Spadaro, October 6-November 8, 1997 (Box V2)
  - Mark Dolejs, September 23-October 4, 1997 (Box V2)
  - Jacob Colley, May 25-July 2, 1997 (Box V2)
  - Broadway Brochures, 1997 (Box V2)
  - Photographs, undated (Box V2)
  - Comprehensive Records, 1992-2001 (Box V3)
  - Photographs, 1998-2000 (Box V3)
  - Photographs, 2000-2002 (Box V3)
  - Major Attractions: Restaurant Menus, 2005-2006 (Box V3)
  - Slides from President Reagan's visit, February, 1988 (Box V4)
- Policy and Manuals, 1974-2006, 3 boxes
  Contains upper-level administrative records, policy documents and manuals for the Union proper, as well as manuals from various committees and for committee chairpersons.
  - Manuals and Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box P1)
  - Manuals and Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box P1)
  - Past Publicity, 1990 (Box P2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box P2)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box P2)
  - University Union Board Minutes, 1996-1998 (Box P2)
  - Policy Manual, 1982 (Box P3)
  - Policy Guidelines, 1982-1983 (Box P3)
  - Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box P3)
  - Minutes, 2001 (Box P3)
  - Minutes, 2005-2006 (Box P3)
  - Chairperson's Manual, 2000-2001 (Box P3)
  - Chairperson's Manual, 2004-2005 (Box P3)
  - Officer List, 1963-2003 (Box P3)
- Scrapbooks, 1950-2005, 16 boxes
  Contains scrapbooks, photo albums, and memorabilia from Union-related events, from the 1950s through the 2000s. Some of the events included are visits from: Dionne Warwick, George McGovern, Louis Armstrong, Dave Brubeck, the Kingston Trio, Adlai Stevenson, Hubert Humphrey, Ravi Shankar, and Gerald Ford.
  - Scrapbook, 1965-1966 [2 scrapbooks] (Box S-1)
  - Scrapbook, 1955-1960 (Box S-2)
  - Scrapbook, 1957-1958 (Box S-3)
  - Scrapbook, 1961-1962 (Box S-4)
  - Scrapbook, 1962-1963 (Box S-5)
  - Scrapbook, 1963-1964 (Box S-5)
  - Clippings, 1957-1959 (Box S-6)
  - Clippings, 1957-1958 (Box S-6)
  - Eductional Affairs Committee Minutes, 1959 (Box S-6)
  - Rosters, mailing lists, and correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box S-6)
  - Brochires, 1959-1960 (Box S-6)
  - Scrapbook, circa 1959-1960 (Box S-6)
  - Monthly Time Ledger, 1947-1957 (Box S-7)
  - Monthly Time Ledger, 1957-1967 (Box S-7)
  - Monthly Time Ledger, 1967 (Box S-7)
  - Scrapbook, 1964-1965 (Box S-8)
  - Scrapbook, 1967-1968 [2 scrapbooks] (Box S-9)
  - Performing Arts Scrapbook, 1988-1989 (Box S-10)
  - Broadway Scrapbook, 1989-1990 (Box S-10)
  - Broadway Scrapbook, 1990-1991 (Box S-10)
  - Photographs, undated (Box S-10)
  - Visual Arts Picture Book, undated (Box S-10)
  - Art Signature Book, 1982-1983 (Box S-11)
  - The Family of Man, 1955 (Box S-11)
  - Frank Meadow Sutcliffe, 1985 (Box S-11)
  - Goya to Gauguin, undated (Box S-11)
  - The Camera, 2005 (Box S-11)
  - Union Scrapbook, 1981 (Box S-12)
  - Union Scrapbook, 1982 (Box S-12)
  - Union Scrapbook, 2002 (Box S-12)
  - Performing Arts Scrapbook, 1994 (Box S-12)
  - Chairperson's Manual, 1995-1996 (Box S-13)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1992-1993 (Box S-13)
  - Visual Arts Photo Album, 1981 (Box S-13)
  - Scrapbook (Fall), 1981 (Box S-13)
  - Scrapbook (Fall), 1984 (Box S-13)
  - Sneak Previews, 1991-1992 (Box S-13)
  - Special Series, 1988-1989 (Box S-13)
  - Photo Album, 2002 (Box S-14)
  - Photographs, undated (Box S-14)
  - Scrapbook, 1982-1983 (Box S-15)
  - Scrapbook (Spring), 1984 (Box S-15)
  - Scrapbook (Fall), 1985 (Box S-15)
  - Scrapbook (Spring), 1985 (Box S-15)
  - Scrapbook, 2005 (Box S-15)
  - Fine Arts Scrapbook, 1957-1962 (Box S-15)
  - Visual Arts Scrapbook, 1982 (Box S-15)
  - Scrapbook, 1990s (Box S-16)
  - Scrapbook, 1990s (Box S-16)
  - Cable 13 scrapbook, circa 1982-1986 (Box S-17)
- Audio-Visual Materials, 1 box
  - "Mornings at Seven," 1981 Oct. 16 (2-inch video reel) (Box AV-1)
  - "Mornings at Seven," 1981 Dec. 30 (2-inch video reel) (Box AV-1)
  - "One Mo' Time," undated (2-inch video reel) (Box AV-1)
  - "Mornings at Seven," 1981 Aug. 27 (audio reel) (Box AV-1)
  - "Noises Off," undated (audio reel) (Box AV-1)
  - "Biloxi Blues," 1986 Mar. 10 (audio reel) (Box AV-1)
  - Untitled, undated (audio reel) (Box AV-1)
  - Vinyl 45 record: Stephen Willoughby (Box AV-1)
  - Tony Schwartz Sounds "New York," undated (audiocassette) (Box AV-1)
  - Meetings, 1988 (4 micro-cassettes) (Box AV-1)
- Publicity/Printed Material 1969-1980s, 1 box
  - Various publicity posters and printed material, such as brochures. (Box 55)
- Electronic (Born Digital) Material, 3 disks
  - 3 Diskettes (Box AV-1)
- Accession UA2015-0044 (unprocessed), 1976-2013, undated
  - Graphic Arts Committee Visitors Register, East Campus Library Gallery, 1976-1980 (Box 56)
  - Photographs of Union fall and spring retreats, N.Y. alumni brunch, retirement party for Bill Griffith, Broadway at Duke receptions, other events, 1990-2004, undated (Box 56)
  - Oktoberfest, Union alumni retreat, other event slides, 1984-1990, undated (Box 56)
  - Audiovisual recordings of films/performances including Chevy Chase Jazz Ensemble, Checking Out, Odd Man Out, Rent, the Club, A Lion's Tale, and several unlabeled, undated (Box 56)
  - Duke Jazz at DUU socks, undated (Box 56)
  - Scavenger Haunt, License to Hunt Homecoming Scav Hunt, and Midnight Mulan Sing-along t-shirts, 2012-2013 (Box 56)
  - Floppy disks, zip disks, and electronic content (Box E-Recs Queue 3)